## **CONOR PARRISH**

Software Expert, Entrepreneur, Technical Leader

# conorparrish.com

720-209-5425 conor.parrish@me.com Denver, CO

### Summary

I am a software expert with an entrepreneurial focus. I have experience architecting applications and efficiently building them into profitable software products. Through starting my own companies, I have gained the ability to use customer needs to drive product development. I thrive most in small collaborative teams, and I work to make an immediate, positive impact.

#### Education

University of Colorado Boulder - B.S. Computer Science, May 2018

### Experience

Co-Founder, ShipScout - 2020 - 2022

Bootstrapped an eCommerce app from an idea, to an MVP, to a growing and profitable product, and ultimately sold it. Drove profitability by building extremely low-cost and scalable APIs.

Senior Software Engineer, Yonomi/Allegion; Boulder, CO — 2019 - present Leading software contributor to the next-gen ultra-scalable IoT platform which led to Allegion's 2020 acquisition of Yonomi.

Co-Founder, Hearth; Boulder, CO - 2017 - 2019

Bootstrapped the development of a smart home hardware product from the ground up through rigorous customer development, project management, and coding work.

### Software

Typescript/JavaScript, Rust, Serverless & Event-Driven Design, more I excel at identifying the best software design and tools for each use case. In addition to software architecture, I adapt quickly to different languages and frameworks in order to build fast. The result is an ability to meet customer needs through calculated usage of software.

#### Interests

I am passionate about the outdoors, especially skiing and mountaineering. I enjoy traveling, especially to National Parks and for hiking and biking. I play the guitar and love to run with my dog, Arlo.